(Q1) MARTHA: Hi Alex. It's Martha Clines here. James White gave me your number.
I hope you don't mind me calling you.
ALEX: Of course not. ALEX：
How are you, Martha?
MARTHA: Good thanks. MARTHA：
I'm ringing because I need a bit of advice.
ALEX: Oh yeah. ALEX：What about?
MARTHA: The training you did at JPNW a few years ago. MARTHA：
I'm applying for the same thing.
ALEX: Oh right. ALEX：
[Example] Yes, I did mine in 2014.
Best thing I ever did.
I'm still working there.
MARTHA: Really? MARTHA：
What are you doing?
[Q1答案句 + Q1干扰项] ALEX: Well, now I work in the customer services department but I did my initial training in Finance.
I stayed there for the first two years and then moved to where I am now.
(Q2) MARTHA: That's the same department I'm applying for.
Did you enjoy it?
ALEX: I was pretty nervous to begin with.
[Q2答案句： math /Math / Mathematics] I didn't do well in my exams at school and I was really worried because I failed Maths.
But it didn't actually matter because I did lots of courses on the job.
(Q3) [Q3答案句] MARTHA: Did you get a diploma at the end of your trainee period? I'm hoping to do the one in business skills.
ALEX: Yes. That sounds good.
[代词指代， 答案已经说过了] I took the one on IT skills but I wish I'd done that one instead.
MARTHA: OK, that's good to know.
(Q4) What about the other trainees?
How did you get on with them?
[Q4答案句+Q4干扰项] ALEX: There were about 20 of us who started at the same time and we were all around the same age - I was 18 and there was only one person younger than me, who was 17. ALEX：
The rest were between 18 and 20.
I made some good friends.
(Q5) MARTHA: I've heard lots of good things about the training at JPNW. MARTHA：
It seems like there are a lot of opportunities there.
ALEX: Yeah, definitely. ALEX：
Because of its size you can work in loads of different areas within the organisation.
[Q5干扰项] MARTHA: What about pay? I know you get a lower minimum wage than regular employees.
[Q5答案句] ALEX: That's right - which isn't great.   But you get the same number of days' holiday as everyone else.
And the pay goes up massively if they offer you a job at the end of the training period.
(Q6) MARTHA: Yeah, but I'm not doing it for the money - it's the experience I think will be really useful.
[跟定位词] Everyone says by the end of the year you gain so much confidence.
ALEX: You're right.
That's the most useful part about it.
There's a lot of variety too.
You're given lots of different things to do.
I enjoyed it all - I didn't even mind the studying.
[Q6答案句，一方提出，另一方表态 = 代词指代] MARTHA: Do you have to spend any time in college?ALEX: Yes, one day each month.
So you get lots of support from both your tutor and your manager.
(Q7) [company出现] MARTHA: That's good. And the company is easy to get to, isn't it?
[Q7答案句： location 。  ... is a real advantage = ... is convenient] ALEX: Yes, it's very close to the train station so the location's a real advantage.
(Q8) ALEX: Have you got a date for your interview yet? ALEX：
MARTHA: Yes, it's on the 23rd of this month. MARTHA：
ALEX: So long as you're well prepared there's nothing to worry about. ALEX：
Everyone's very friendly.
[Q8跟定位： wear] MARTHA: I am not sure what I should wear. What do you think?
[Q8答案句， 否定 = nothing too ... , like ... = don't wear] ALEX: Nothing too casual - like jeans, for example.
If you've got a nice jacket, wear that with a skirt or trousers.
MARTHA: OK. MARTHA：
Thanks.
(Q9) Any other tips?
ALEX: Erm, well I know it's really obvious but arrive in plenty of time.
[Q9答案句： hate people who are ... = don't be ...] They hate people who are late.
So make sure you know exactly where you have to get to.
(Q10) [Q10答案句] And one other useful piece of advice my manager told me before I had the interview for this job - is to smile.
Even if you feel terrified.
It makes people respond better to you.
MARTHA: I'll have to practise doing that in the mirror!
ALEX: Yeah - well, good luck.
Let me know if you need any more information.
MARTHA: Thanks very much.